<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <!-- Translated Texts, ordered by origin text -->
  <content contentuid="hg89c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">A magic poisoner's kit includes the vials, chemicals, and other equipment necessary for the creation of poisons that do necrotic damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hg87c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">A poisoner's kit includes the vials, chemicals, and other equipment necessary for the creation of poisons</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3643" version="1">A poisoner's kit includes the vials, chemicals, and other equipment necessary for the creation of poisons</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7772" version="1">Actor</content>
  <content contentuid="hg72c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Advantage Savingthrow Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7775" version="1">Alert to the hidden traps and secret doors found in many dungeons, you gain the following benefits: You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) and Intelligence (Investigation) checks made to detect the presence of secret doors. You have advantage on saving throws made to avoid or resist traps. You have resistance to the damage dealt by traps. You can search for traps while traveling at a normal pace, instead of only at a slow pace. | You have advantage on perception and investigation checks and Resistance to slashing damage| </content>
  <content contentuid="hc10571e2g30e8g4c86gb988ga9a234b4c0b5" version="1">Dodge</content>
  <content contentuid="hg94c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Dodge Action</content>
  <content contentuid="hb93172abga0feg4f07g9995g95eb0d815054" version="1">Dodge Action - Dwarven Fortitude |Requires combat|</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060c9b54efda13e38216ce76654" version="1">Dragon Hide</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060c9b54efda13e38216ce76658" version="1">Dragon Hide Claws</content>
  <content contentuid="hg5636871g90b2g4f18gab29g0a0a8f3fbdce" version="1">Drow Assassin Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7774" version="1">Dungeon Delver</content>
  <content contentuid="h0111754eg8648g431fg89f4g78cf75db7e08" version="1">Dwarven Fortitude</content>
  <content contentuid="hg64c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Altertümlicher Adept</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7743" version="1">Elven Accuracy</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7751" version="1">Elven Accuracy: Charisma</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7745" version="1">Elven Accuracy: Dexterity</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3635" version="1">Elven Accuracy: Dexterity</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7747" version="1">Elven Accuracy: Intelligence</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7749" version="1">Elven Accuracy: Wisdom</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7766" version="1">Everybody's Friend </content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3637" version="1">Fire Aura</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7762" version="1">Flames Of Phlegethos</content>
  <content contentuid="hg75c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Flames Of Phlegethos: Charisma</content>
  <content contentuid="hg74c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Flames Of Phlegethos: Intelligence</content>
  <content contentuid="hc10671e2g30e8g4c86gb988ga9a234b4c0b5" version="1">Focus on defending yourself and avoiding incoming strikes. Attacks against you are made with disadvantage until the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg66c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Heavy Armor Master</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7753" version="1">Infernal Constitution</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7770" version="1">Luck Points</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7768" version="1">Lucky Feat </content>
  <content contentuid="hg59c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Magic Drow Assassin Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="hg5848970g49d4g4d9agb7bfg50ce6a8c581f" version="1">Magic Poisoner's Kit for Assassins</content>
  <content contentuid="hg4336871g90b2g4f18gab29g0a0a8f3fbdce" version="1">Magic Poisoner's Kit For Assassins</content>
  <content contentuid="hg61c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Magic Poisoner's Kit. Combine with items to create poisons and other items. MagicPoisonerKit + Basic Poison = Magic Drow Assassin Poison (Necrotic Dmg); MagicPoisonerKit + Healing Potion = Basic Poison (2), MagicPoisonerKit+ Greater Healing = Basic Poison (4)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3638" version="1">Melee attackers take 1d4 of fire damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hg99d268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Observant</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7776" version="1">Poisoner</content>
  <content contentuid="hg5548970g49d4g4d9agb7bfg50ce6a8c581f" version="1">Poisoner's Kit for Assassins</content>
  <content contentuid="hg4236871g90b2g4f18gab29g0a0a8f3fbdce" version="1">Poisoner's Kit For Assassins</content>
  <content contentuid="hg34c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Poisoner's Kit. Combine with items to create poisons and other items. PoisonerKit + Basic Poison = Wyvern Poison; PoisonerKit + Wyvern Poison = Drow Poison; PoisonerKit + Healing Potion = Basic Poison (2), + Greater Healing = Basic Poison (4)</content>
  <content contentuid="hg70c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Polearm Master</content>
  <content contentuid="hg81c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dexterity 13 or higher. You are expert at slinking through shadows. You gain the following benefits: • You can try to hide when you are only lightly obscured from the creature from which you are hiding. • When you are hidden from a creature and miss it with a ranged weapon attack, making the attack doesn't reveal your position. • Dim light doesn't impose disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) bonuses made with sight."
data "ExtraDescription" "If you miss with a ranged weapon attack you automatically attempt to hide. When in light obscured environments you have advantage on perception checks"</content>
  <content contentuid="hg69c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dexterity 13 or higher. You are expert at slinking through shadows. You gain the following benefits: • You can try to hide when you are only lightly obscured from the creature from which you are hiding.• When you are hidden from a creature and miss it with a ranged weapon attack, making the attack doesn't reveal your position.• Dim light doesn't impose disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) bonuses made with sight.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg77c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf or a Small race. You are uncommonly nimble for your race. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Dexterity score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Increase your walking speed by 5 feet. You gain proficiency in the Acrobatics skill. You have advantage on any Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check you make to escape from being grappled.[You gain advantage on Acrobotics skill checks]</content>
  <content contentuid="hg79c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf or a Small race. You are uncommonly nimble for your race. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Dexterity score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Increase your walking speed by 5 feet. You gain proficiency in the Athletics skill. You have advantage on any Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check you make to escape from being grappled.[You gain advantage on Athletics skill checks]</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7765" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf or a Small race. You are uncommonly nimble for your race. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Strength or Dexterity score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Increase your walking speed by 5 feet. You gain proficiency in the Acrobatics or Athletics skill (your choice). You have advantage on any Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check you make to escape from being grappled.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg91c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf or a Small race. You are uncommonly nimble for your race. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Strength score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Increase your walking speed by 5 feet. You gain proficiency in the Acrobatics skill. You have advantage on any Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check you make to escape from being grappled.[You gain advantage on Acrobotics skill checks]</content>
  <content contentuid="hg93c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf or a Small race. You are uncommonly nimble for your race. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Strength score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Increase your walking speed by 5 feet. You gain proficiency in the Athletics skill. You have advantage on any Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check you make to escape from being grappled.[You gain advantage on Athletics skill checks]</content>
  <content contentuid="hb7cdfa17g2c06g4149g958dg0a886658a3b9" version="1">Prerequisite: Dwarf. You have the blood of dwarf heroes flowing through your veins. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Constitution score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you take the Dodge action in combat, you can spend one Hit Die to heal yourself. Roll the die, add your Constitution modifier, and regain a number of hit points equal to the total (minimum of 1).</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7767" version="1">Prerequisite: Half-elf. You develop your magnetic personality to ease your way through the world. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Charisma score by 1, up to a maximum of 20. You gain proficiency in the Deception and Persuasion skills. If you’re already proficient in either skill, your proficiency bonus is doubled for any check you make with that skill [You gain proficiency and +2 bonus to the roll]. </content>
  <content contentuid="hg65c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Voraussetzung ist: Zaubern oder Paktmagie. Durch das Studium okkulter Überlieferungen hast du eine urzeitliche Macht in dir freigesetzt: Du erlernst eine eldritische Beschwörungsoption deiner Wahl aus der Klasse der Hexenmeister. Wenn die Beschwörung eine Voraussetzung hat, kannst du diese Beschwörung nur wählen, wenn du ein Hexenmeister bist und nur, wenn du die Voraussetzung erfüllst. Immer wenn du eine Stufe aufsteigst, kannst du die Beschwörung durch eine andere aus der Hexenmeisterklasse ersetzen.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7754" version="1">Prerequisite: Tiefling. Fiendish blood runs strong in you, unlocking a resilience akin to that possessed by some fiends. You gain the following benefits: 
    Increase your Constitution score by 1, up to a maximum of 20. You have resistance to cold damage and poison damage. You have advantage on saving throws against being poisoned.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7763" version="1">Prerequisite: Tiefling. You learn to call on hellfire to serve your commands. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Intelligence or Charisma score by 1, to a maximum of 20. When you roll fire damage for a spell you cast, you can reroll any roll of 1 on the fire damage dice, but you must use the new roll, even if it is another 1. Whenever you cast a spell that deals fire damage, you can cause flames to wreathe you until the end of your next turn. The flames don’t harm you or your possessions, and they shed bright light out to 30 feet and dim light for an additional 30 feet. While the flames are present, any creature within 5 feet of you that hits you with a melee attack takes 1d4 fire damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg99e268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Quick to notice details of your environment, you gain the following benefits:
Increase your Intelligence or Wisdom score by 1, to a maximum of 20.
If you can see a creature's mouth while it is speaking a language you understand, you can interpret what it's saying by reading its lips.
You have a +5 bonus to your passive Wisdom (Perception) and passive Intelligence (Investigation) scores.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7757" version="1">Resistance Cold</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7755" version="1">Resistance Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3640" version="1">Skill Expert</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7773" version="1">Skilled at mimicry and dramatics, you gain the following benefits: Increase your Charisma score by 1, to a maximum of 20. You have advantage on Charisma (Deception) and Charisma (Performance) checks when trying to pass yourself off as a different person. You can mimic the speech of another person or the sounds made by other creatures. You must have heard the person speaking, or heard the creature make the sound, for at least 1 minute. A successful Wisdom (Insight) check contested by your Charisma (Deception) check allows a listener to determine that the effect is faked.| You have skill, and advantage, with Deception and Performance checks| </content>
  <content contentuid="hg68c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker</content>
  <content contentuid="hg80c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker</content>
  <content contentuid="hg84c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker Feat: Hide</content>
  <content contentuid="hg82c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker Feat: Ranged</content>
  <content contentuid="hg82c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker Feat: Vision</content>
  <content contentuid="hg83c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Skulker Feat: When you are hidden from a creature and miss it with a ranged weapon attack, making the attack doesn't reveal your position |If you miss with a ranged attack you will attempt to hide|</content>
  <content contentuid="hg83c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Dim light doesn't impose disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) bonuses made with sight |In dim light you have advantage on perception checks|</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7764" version="1">Squat Nimbleness</content>
  <content contentuid="hg92c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Squat Nimbleness:  +1 Str + Athletics Prof</content>
  <content contentuid="hg76c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Squat Nimbleness: +1 Dex + Acrobatics Prof</content>
  <content contentuid="hg78c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Squat Nimbleness: +1 Dex + Athletics Prof</content>
  <content contentuid="hg90c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Squat Nimbleness: +1 Str + Acrobatics Prof</content>
  <content contentuid="hg88c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Summon Magic Poisoner's Kit</content>
  <content contentuid="hg86c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Summon Poisoner's Kit</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3642" version="1">Summon Poisoner's Kit</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7752" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Charisma score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once. </content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7746" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Dexterity score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3636" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Dexterity score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7744" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom or Charisma score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7748" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Intelligence  score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7750" version="1">The accuracy of elves is legendary, especially that of elf archers and spellcasters. You have uncanny aim with attacks that rely on precision rather than brute force. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Wisdom score by 1, to a maximum of 20. Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7771" version="1">Until your next turn you have advantage on attack rolls, ability checks or saving throws. Your enemies have disadvantage on their attack rolls against you. You regain your expended luck points when you finish a long rest. </content>
  <content contentuid="hg57c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Weapons coated with Drow Assassin Poison deal an extra 1d6 of poison damage for a period of one minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg60c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">Weapons coated with Magic Drow Assassin Poison deal an extra 1d6 of NECROTIC poison damage for a period of one minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg71c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">When you take the Attack action and attack with only a glaive, halberd, quarterstaff, or spear, you can use a bonus action to make a melee attack with the opposite end of the weapon. This attack uses the same ability modifier as the primary attack. The weapon's damage die for this attack is a d4, and it deals bludgeoning damage.
While you are wielding a glaive, halberd, pike, quarterstaff, or spear, other creatures provoke an opportunity attack from you when they enter the reach you have with that weapon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb93172abga0feg4f07g9995g95eb0d815055" version="1">When you take the dodge action you also regain class hit die + constitution modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg95c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">When you take the Dodge action, you focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated or if your speed drops to 0.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3639" version="1">Whenever you have advantage on an attack roll using Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma, you can reroll one of the dice once.</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060-c9b5-4efd-a13e-38216ce76656" version="1">Wood Elf Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060c9b54efda13e38216ce76659" version="1">You can grow retractable claws from the tips of your fingers. Extending or retracting the claws requires no action. The claws are natural weapons, which you can use to make unarmed strikes. If you hit with them, you deal slashing damage equal to 1d4 + your Strength modifier, instead of the normal bludgeoning damage for an unarmed strike</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7777" version="1">You can prepare and deliver deadly poisons, gaining the following benefits: When you make a damage roll, you ignore resistance to poison damage. You can coat a weapon in poison as a bonus action, instead of an action.     You gain proficiency with the poisoner's kit if you don't already have it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg85c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">You can try to hide when you are only lightly obscured from the creature from which you are hiding. |In dim light you have advantage on stealth checks|</content>
  <content contentuid="hg67c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">You can use your armor to deflect strikes that would kill others. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Strength by 1, to a maximum of 20. When wearing heavy armor, bludgeoning, slashing and piercing damage you take from non-magical weapons is reduced by 3.</content>
  <content contentuid="hg73c268ag49b0g48cbgaf37g76cec2369e9e" version="1">You have advantage on saving throws against being poisoned</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d607cc2g0131g477cgbd6bg89eb004a3641" version="1">You have honed your proficiency with particular skills, granting you the following benefits: Increase one ability score of your choice by 1, to a maximum of 20. You gain proficiency in one skill of your choice.
Choose one skill in which you have proficiency. You gain expertise with that skill, which means your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make with it. The skill you choose must be one that isn't already benefiting from a feature, such as Expertise, that doubles your proficiency bonus.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7769" version="1">You have inexplicable luck that seems to kick in at just the right moment. You have 3 luck points. Whenever you make an attack roll, an ability check, or a saving throw, you can spend one luck point to roll an additional d20. You can also spend one luck point when an attack roll is made against you. In combat you activate your luck. Until your next turn you have advantage on attack rolls, ability checks or saving throws. Your enemies have disadvantage on their attack rolls against you. If more than one creature spends a luck point to influence the outcome of a roll, the points cancel each other out; no additional dice are rolled. You regain your expended luck points when you finish a long rest. </content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7758" version="1">You have resistance to cold damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hff81d1fdg0b49g4e93gb796g9f68623b7756" version="1">You have resistance to poison damage</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060-c9b5-4efd-a13e-38216ce76657" version="1">You learn the magic of the primeval woods, which are revered and protected by your people. You learn one Druid cantrip of your choice. You also learn the Longstrider and Pass Without Trace spells, each of which you can cast once without expending a spell slot. You regain the ability to cast these two spells in this way when you finish a long rest. Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for all three spells.</content>
  <content contentuid="5fea8060c9b54efda13e38216ce76655" version="1">You manifest scales and claws reminiscent of your draconic ancestors. You gain the following benefits: Increase your Strength, Constitution, or Charisma score by 1, up to a maximum of 20.
While you aren't wearing armor, you can calculate your AC as 13 + your Dexterity modifier. You can use a shield and still gain this benefit. You can grow retractable claws from the tips of your fingers. Extending or retracting the claws requires no action. The claws are natural weapons, which you can use to make unarmed strikes. If you hit with them, you deal slashing damage equal to 1d4 + your Strength modifier</content>
</contentList>