<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <content contentuid="hcc8fd7c0gd034g442cga587g6b2a81d85777" version="1">Vom Griff dieser Streitaxt bis zum Axtkopf erstrecken sich üppige Sussurwurzeln. Sie sehnt sich nach Magie und bringt jede Kreatur, die sie berührt, zum Schweigen.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha24ede63gc590g4225g985ag49acac2cc111" version="1">Gesättigte Sussur-Streitaxt</content>
  <content contentuid="h237f9f15g6035g4545g9f1dg807cdcfad4e7" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this daggers's hilt into the blade head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h060321cdgd534g4474ga87ag5152c957e5d7" version="1">Sated Sussur Dagger</content>
  <content contentuid="h19df3e5fg68dcg44a8gbe4cg455b768c507e" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend throughout this flail into the striking head. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd88945b8g0804g48f4g9445ge339d8763c57" version="1">Sated Sussur Flail</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfb47c6dgf3f0g4eb4ga68eg3de3c5cb54cd" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this glaive's handle into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha018a497g9911g4cb6g9236g6b7c5ac14ea7" version="1">Sated Sussur Glaive</content>
  <content contentuid="h41f06d40g96ecg460fg8a25g8c5e36242f38" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this handle's shaft into the axe head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9ed8ba0g7eb5g4bd4gbf30g15071d8b401f" version="1">Sated Sussur Greataxe</content>
  <content contentuid="hff2a2e6fg4e76g4e30g9d26g2a7c39e443dc" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this halberd's shaft into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bd8e140g9a25g4a95g8fbcg5cbf87eb0442" version="1">Sated Sussur Halberd</content>
  <content contentuid="h26754820gc704g4f96g82a0g409b91e46bfa" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend throughout this greatclub. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h030cdbdcgc56fg4622g9ff1g87b4a6ebe736" version="1">Sated Sussur Greatclub</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b35e159g084fg4574gaaa6g30234aea4836" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this javelin's shaft into the tip itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d204c17g42c4g4309g81e3g04feac30ec70" version="1">Sated Sussur Javelin</content>
  <content contentuid="haa9c1f96gf18fg4542ga388g78306bf766e1" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this hammer's handle into the head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e6aaa0dg4c0cg4950g99a0g12b10dd28003" version="1">Sated Sussur Light Hammer</content>
  <content contentuid="hfb5d86b8g5de7g4230gb538g6b3e05142e47" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this sword's hilt into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcdad81b1gd6a1g4189gb477ge717b1596e48" version="1">Sated Sussur Longsword</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b23b458g080eg4b7bg9ea6g6f2702ec3b9b" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this mace's handle into the mace head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h73518635g2cb1g464bgad75g73b7a0256b1a" version="1">Sated Sussur Mace</content>
  <content contentuid="had1e40a8g4265g403agaab0g7f4deaa2e4c2" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this maul's handle into the wedge-shaped head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h03fd5fc9g9e7fg4edfgabd6gd4b7b83d60dc" version="1">Sated Sussur Maul</content>
  <content contentuid="hcf747e52g5cb2g44c0gb3bfg901470b611f5" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this morningstar's handle into the spikes themselves. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a71dc3ag7924g4970ga421g6e2b0f05bb8a" version="1">Sated Sussur Morningstar</content>
  <content contentuid="h030bcc58g8496g4ea5g96f1gcff1e4ccae30" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this pike's handle into the tip itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf742f27gbb0ag49bdga5b6ge3eeb756e75d" version="1">Sated Sussur Pike</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e106420g39d2g4145g9fbdg13404ccf0ff2" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend throughout this quarterstaff. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="he67b3553g031cg4a86g9c87g218fb854d16c" version="1">Sated Sussur Quarterstaff</content>
  <content contentuid="habd972b8g0b23g42eag9d6eg79080a1a73e4" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this rapier's hilt into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h62789193g109dg4a17gafd8g928ee7302192" version="1">Sated Sussur Rapier</content>
  <content contentuid="hf458adc3gcf05g43cdgaf98g5838b12771be" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this scimitar's hilt into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cbcced8g428fg4f79gb6c0g89ee8e44094e" version="1">Sated Sussur Scimitar</content>
  <content contentuid="h6127a74fg7612g4054g8450gd2c3b4fb7448" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this shortsword's hilt into the blade itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7318f83cg3875g4fd4g96c2g983a114d38dd" version="1">Sated Sussur Shortsword</content>
  <content contentuid="ha38d636bg36ffg47cegabc7g2527fffeabce" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this spear's shaft into the tip itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h23452237g3544g47begb7d9g4bfc24f08a73" version="1">Sated Sussur Spear</content>
  <content contentuid="h1da3c5c4g7c64g4a27ga401ge90afd18bbde" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this trident's shaft into the pokers themselves. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a9f656eg4259g4605gba9ega7757ce00122" version="1">Sated Sussur Trident</content>
  <content contentuid="h66fc7a46ga582g4024ga542gb70c1e68414a" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this war pick's shaft into the point itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ef6c789g5dc0g4b0ag9fffg5dfb2595780b" version="1">Sated Sussur War Pick</content>
  <content contentuid="h73e66d37ga707g4576ga7b5g7159aff1c4b9" version="1">Sated Sussur roots extend from this warhammer's shaft into the head itself. It yearns to drink magic, silencing every creature it strikes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a94f364g0e3dg4ae3gb37fge4c370f0eaa4" version="1">Sated Sussur Warhammer</content>
  <content contentuid="a7bcef1c-3cc3-4ac9-aefd-aa75c9ec8bb0" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this battleaxe's handle into the axe head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ebbf05fg5b96g4e71g822fga969cfc77db6" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Battleaxe</content>
  <content contentuid="h2121917cg0a21g46efgbe4egc471da8ab6c4" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this dagger's shaft into the head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c342378g6e3bg41b4ga7d5g4df97fcad07a" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Dagger</content>
  <content contentuid="h40f5fdcagee46g4096g9f59g1d50668f2c35" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend throughout this flail into the striking head. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfda1983eg7256g4134g89afgc8e5c5f8556b" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Flail</content>
  <content contentuid="h0089e1c0g18ebg4917ga78bg5aa878057bc7" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this glaive's handle into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcbea2debgf201g44e7ga860g2a8a230920c1" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Glaive</content>
  <content contentuid="h75b0eac8g35cag45cfg9c48g5ef92ae49afb" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this handle's shaft into the axe head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h13898b42g3c9fg4fbbgad24g87c6927cb06d" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Greataxe</content>
  <content contentuid="h2ef29fb6gb6f3g468agbf72gb9a4cea4d78e" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this halberd's shaft into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hca0fe266gb491g401egb271g86190ac8f2fa" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Halberd</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e34afb4gc22eg4667g8f47ga9af2a0f56ed" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend throughout this greatclub. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf6f409edg16bdg4428gb89cgae8c6c911ad5" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Greatclub</content>
  <content contentuid="heffd08ecgb803g4854gbc45g4e7aed765b60" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this javelin's shaft into the tip itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd8b5fb2g0cafg48f6gb086g500e131abb67" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Javelin</content>
  <content contentuid="h120a328egd40ag43ffg936bg102bb75e5ce1" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this hammer's handle into the head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7285c7d1ge098g4d9dg9e78g7512ebf1d9b8" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Light Hammer</content>
  <content contentuid="h5871eacdgdde3g43a0gbbdcg84f50e1b1cd8" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this sword's hilt into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h363578a2g46c5g44b2ga62fg5177895d11f6" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Longsword</content>
  <content contentuid="hf7f63479ga947g41aagb61fg2a82f2344be8" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this mace's handle into the mace head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h78c15270gc33dg43f5g9cd4g584ac3428445" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Mace</content>
  <content contentuid="h671572e6g97c0g4084g9d55ge3630a1ec38f" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this maul's handle into the wedge-shaped head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9e11596ga6e8g4ce1g8d10g6be8856d311a" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Maul</content>
  <content contentuid="h359926d2g6f6fg4c83gb653g7e7c054e12b6" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this morningstar's handle into the spikes themselves. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21fbbc00g8b81g4ec8ga25eg53e163200138" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Morningstar</content>
  <content contentuid="h499826aag29acg4a63ga242gd377fb23a955" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this pike's handle into the tip itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bc1a727g0e0eg45d7gab68g009cef77f849" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Pike</content>
  <content contentuid="he89db350gc4b7g479agb864g346da745a144" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend throughout this quarterstaff. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b41c2c0gaab6g4614g80ccg1289418ddd67" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Quarterstaff</content>
  <content contentuid="h2be34ce1gfc25g4745gb144ga9673ac0a8f5" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this rapier's hilt into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7896200g237fg4d08gb9abg6a7021743fbf" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Rapier</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb81a837g3a87g4853g85f3gbdae2eb15d63" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this scimitar's hilt into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h12589acdgf9d6g4600gb4e2g61bbebd1ff9c" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Scimitar</content>
  <content contentuid="h70efedb7g7f36g437fg8149g0b05f58e0686" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this shortsword's hilt into the blade itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h833eb13bg0073g4096gb13fgcb13ff786e52" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Shortsword</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d5f489fgae6cg4e8ag882ag3cfd2bf1a49c" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this spear's shaft into the tip itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="he2722002g46cdg452bg836egd9ee2771c6ab" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Spear</content>
  <content contentuid="h4aca47b8g50ecg447dgaddagaaa50f5ed7cd" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this trident's shaft into the pokers themselves. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbc19098ag3c77g4e86gbe6cg80866d9b3c9d" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Trident</content>
  <content contentuid="h5159d75dgc8a0g4e14gb882ge74a6ebbffaf" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this war pick's shaft into the point itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b359e4bg420ag4c42ga4f8ge4de45ea0d6a" version="1">Thirsting Sussur War Pick</content>
  <content contentuid="he135d181ga4d7g4e8fg8022gdc1ca8dd62b6" version="1">Thirsting Sussur roots extend from this warhammer's shaft into the head itself. It drains the magic of creatures it strikes, silencing them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h60b906d7gd6f4g44f3g9888g935b5d612f1f" version="1">Thirsting Sussur Warhammer</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d38dee2gb211g4cb3gbab8g98fddd322e61" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this battleaxe's handle into the axe head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h33e9d25ag0e76g454fgba39g051059f1bf78" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Battleaxe</content>
  <content contentuid="h673fe69bgda40g4ac2g9d6cgc859eed827b8" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this dagger's hilt into the head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="he578ca66geb08g4b31g9fcfgc552fe3fee55" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Dagger</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3a97c4cg535dg4309gbf83g4ece61650cab" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend throughout this flail into the striking head. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e96c6f7g0fd0g474eg8f1dg6b31001adf0d" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Flail</content>
  <content contentuid="h3ef7a6a8gacbcg4207g9152g0a332c58149e" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this glaive's handle into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a9f026bg93cdg4dd3g93afg75d734a5f1c0" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Glaive</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a4b516cg4834g4adfgba32g34be2824844f" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this handle's shaft into the axe head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d53c0e2g5a29g4762g980dgf14f29a1cd12" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Greataxe</content>
  <content contentuid="h894865bbgc5c7g4c87gbf22ga6fb129ab990" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this halberd's shaft into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hef21e2c8g6c2fg4d6agb96eg57bc1ed98d8d" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Halberd</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ad4d429ga883g4211g946ag35a6fd3a19c0" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend throughout this greatclub. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd67e084bg452cg447eg9860gd4c9d30559d1" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Greatclub</content>
  <content contentuid="h4becdbe2g95aeg4537gacaag4df0a9a7021d" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this javelin's shaft into the tip itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hba6abbabga794g44e3g8bcbg90a319280827" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Javelin</content>
  <content contentuid="h67ea06b4ge0f0g41abg8c43gb2141386a34b" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this hammer's handle into the head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdee79a03g7f07g4a2bga1f8g3f0514f09f49" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Light Hammer</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3ca261agce6ag4317g8adbgdab6252a39c6" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this sword's hilt into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h51cade9dg9c76g487dg802eg0d4103c0449b" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Longsword</content>
  <content contentuid="hac8410e0gcb5eg4b77g844eg81b559f086e5" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this mace's handle into the mace head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc7ceac79g66b1g425cgba9egf2b22f042a59" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Mace</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4964c82gb62ag44ddg9cc1gb39e0d08c05f" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this maul's handle into the wedge-shaped head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h69e6975bgab14g465aga936ge8750ecf2629" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Maul</content>
  <content contentuid="h6acaae02g34b8g4e9fg9104g39f2ec86566f" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this morningstar's handle into the spikes themselves. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e52e9eeg9d0fg4edeg85ccg724db20238b9" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Morningstar</content>
  <content contentuid="h37f5e4f8gd349g4ffeg9db9gee7c71913c2a" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this pike's handle into the tip itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4384facfg8801g46ccgb38ag7496427909dd" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Pike</content>
  <content contentuid="he251330fg121dg4987ga414g7bb34db75342" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend throughout this quarterstaff. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h83be9bd9ga384g463cgbb81g414b4c75f6c1" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Quarterstaff</content>
  <content contentuid="h95dd6e5bgeabag49cbga73bge141b0cf6de3" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this rapier's hilt into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8bdc6812g2e78g48a3g8474g2262a4749557" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Rapier</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d152652g925cg462aga00agba1347494441" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this scimitar's hilt into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hde9b9d3cg75cfg4c0eg8883g7aa73dc5e30f" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Scimitar</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9bf9fbega405g4fffg9268g76995cad06c8" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this shortsword's hilt into the blade itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75ccb5b8gd669g4460g935bg43afdffc8559" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Shortsword</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f2baf9ag3e2fg42d1gb269g1daad8bc8368" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this spear's shaft into the tip itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h15ab3115ge4d5g442ag983eg7910175d200c" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Spear</content>
  <content contentuid="h69b57153gfd40g4330gbc35g3723bcba72b5" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this trident's shaft into the pokers themselves. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb451e833g4cf6g4f3egbfbdga815f9198264" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Trident</content>
  <content contentuid="h2cb80052g06c1g4b9egb8e4gb7ec5882c6ca" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this war pick's shaft into the point itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbade455geaa6g4cfaga731ga7fd22d684a3" version="1">Ravenous Sussur War Pick</content>
  <content contentuid="hd86c6bdcgcce2g44c5g9b6fg3e4a7dc892ee" version="1">Ravenous Sussur roots extend from this warhammer's shaft into the head itself. It devours the magic of all it strikes leaving nothing but muted bodies behind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h05cd8823g20f5g4973gb2bdg9b54fa94c1ea" version="1">Ravenous Sussur Warhammer</content>
  <content contentuid="h5377ba40gda8bg4517ga5ccg6de44b106a3b" version="1">Sussur Spell Devour</content>
  <content contentuid="h26a62f62gc3d0g491dga5e2g9e98ab545931" version="1">Use the power of the mighty Sussur tree infused with your weapon to nullify any spell of 6th level or lower instantly. If the spell being countered is 7th, 8th or 9th level you must succeed a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Check&lt;/LSTag&gt; to nullify it, the difficulty of which is based on  the spell's Level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae13c725ge5ecg4853gaa2cg189a3a852a06" version="1">Failed Sussur Spell Devour</content>
  <content contentuid="haf4f40a3g6cacg459ag9091g963625ce3148" version="1">Force a creature fail when it casts a spell. Spells of 6th level or lower can always be interrupted. Higher level spells are harder.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4964c477g8580g44cbgad19g7b3409a9e9e0" version="1">Sussur thrown passive 1</content>
  <content contentuid="h37a80ff1gebddg4c37gbac1gc618c5560d25" version="1">Sussur thrown passive 2</content>
  <content contentuid="h8419880bg62b9g423egb121g758b492449d7" version="1">Sussur thrown passive legendary</content>
  <content contentuid="h438de858g5ab2g4f9ag9514g33d0b66b8668" version="1">This passive exists only to enable Sussur weapons to silence when thrown.</content>
</contentList>