<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
  <!-- Translated Texts, ordered by origin text -->
  <content contentuid="ha689d787gaf00g4a24ga9f9gb325e45c466f" version="1">...erstellt vom bösen Lich Icarium dem Schwarzen, war der Zauber einer der ersten, den er während seiner vielen Studien tief in den Grenzen von Cormallen perfektionierte. Er erfuhr, dass er durch die Ausübung seines unheiligen Willens in der Lage war, die Seelen seiner Feinde in einen wirbelnden Wirbel schreiender Geister zu binden.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; – Auszug aus dem &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis" &gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1973d5ag152bg4618g9b2fg65da7dfab625" version="1">...Das Buch der Toten. In Menschenhaut gefesselt und mit dem Blut von Mördern getränkt. Dieses unheilige Buch enthält bizarre Bestattungsriten, Bestattungsformeln und Passagen zur Auferstehung von Dämonen. Es war nie für die Augen der Lebenden gedacht. Es war nie für dich bestimmt. Sie erinnern sich an alte Legenden, die erzählen, dass in den Seiten dieses blasphemischen Buches die Geheimnisse des ewigen Lebens über den Tod hinaus liegen. Wörter schlängeln sich scheinbar über die Seiten des Buches und werden unleserlich, je mehr man versucht, den Text zu übersetzen. Die Kritzeleien bilden gelegentlich zusammenhängende Wörter und laden Sie ein, ihre Geheimnisse herauszufinden ...

&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_DreadOverlord"&gt;...Schreckensherrscher...&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_Aeternusvitae"&gt;...aeternusvitae...&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_OrderOfTheDracolich"&gt;...Orden des Dracolich...&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_SoulHarvest"&gt;...Seelenernte ...&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_GreaterUndead"&gt;..der Größere Untote...&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h97f05e37g9b76g41ddg99ecgcbec5a52e82d" version="1">...die ganze Luft zuckt vor Angst vor seiner böswilligen Anwesenheit. Seine zerstörte Gestalt wird von zwei riesigen Flügeln flankiert, die sich wie ein großer Schatten hinter ihm ausbreiten, und einem Schwanz, an dessen Spitze böse dunkle Flammen sprühen. Seine Augen – zwei Nadelstiche aus rotem Licht, die in unheiliger Energie aus dem Inneren eines drakonischen Schädels flammten – blickten auf uns herab. Die Kultisten schreckten vor dem Dracolich zurück, als der faulige Gestank von Tod und Verfall, der ihn wie ein bösartiges Leichentuch umgab, uns überkam. Für das Versprechen von Wissen und Macht haben wir uns bereitwillig seinem Schrecken und seiner Verzweiflung ergeben.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; – Auszug aus dem &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h19b0db6egf123g46b4gabe9g6066019a89a1" version="1">&lt;i&gt;Vorsicht!&lt;/i&gt; Nicht einmal Verbündete sind vor deiner schrecklichen Macht sicher!</content>
  <content contentuid="h7d7c2b8dga232g4dfcg84e5g51fdd2552894" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Erfordert einen aktiven &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Schild der Seelen&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hde30286fgd1c8g467aga0c0g8e476930ac61" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Der Schleier hat keine Wirkung auf Untote und Konstrukte.</content>
  <content contentuid="heeb102d9gba7eg42f8g9fcfg74ab06e72d99" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Das Ziel muss eine große oder mittelgroße Leiche sein.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf755dc2ege943g48f5ga412gfed334108f46" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Schaltet visuelle Effekte außerhalb des Kampfes aus.</content>
  <content contentuid="h917275ffgd941g46e1g98bcg8c1f9d64084c" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Das Tragen von leichter, mittlerer oder schwerer Rüstung in einem beliebigen Slot schränkt die Fähigkeit ein, gefangene Seelen zurückzuhalten.</content>
  <content contentuid="hca71b50bg04f7g4a22gb7b4g65a2b96f4453" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_NecroticBlade"&gt;Necrotic Armaments&lt;/LSTag&gt; erlaubt es dir, Shillelagh auf deine Waffe zu wirken, ohne eine &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="BonusActionPoint"&gt;Bonusaktion&lt;/LSTag&gt; zu verbrauchen.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1111ecceg9d35g4b0fga57bg2e95edeb4332" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="TAUNTED"&gt;Stacheln Sie&lt;/LSTag&gt; Feinde dazu an, Sie anzugreifen.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f83ad52g448dg4742g9594g887e7e7c6db7" version="1">Ein dunkles Ritual hat diesen Nekromanten in einen wandelnden Seelenmagneten verwandelt, der verlorene Seelen in seinem gefräßigen Seelenschild gefangen hält.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bcac522g7d36g4384ga044g2a829878bb0e" version="1">Ein furchterregender Aspekt des Schreckensfürsten, eine überragende Gestalt des Schreckens und der Verzweiflung.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bbeaddcgba2eg44e8ga5a3g882c9cf97936" version="1">In der Nähe dieser Kreatur ist eine gespenstische Erscheinung aufgetaucht, die sie vor Schaden schützt. Die betroffene Entität hat +[1] zu ihrer &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Rüstungsklasse&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ed1aea0g8133g4e8dg9ac9g05974fa7482a" version="1">Ein gruselig aussehender Kampfstab aus der Wirbelsäule eines Opfers, auf dem ein Schädel thront, der fast lebendig wirkt, da sich der Kiefer bedrohlich in einer beißenden Bewegung bewegt. Es sieht so aus, als könnte es jemandem böse Kopfschmerzen bereiten.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd56eb7ag9481g4ffcga409gaf9b55f4ad66" version="1">In dem vor Ihnen liegenden Buch erscheint eine Passage, die scheinbar einer Quelle außerhalb des Totenbuchs entnommen ist und die sehr trockene Geschichte eines Rechtsstreits zwischen einem Magierkonsortium und einem ihrer Lehrlinge erzählt. „...die Experimente mit nicht genehmigter Magie wurden zu einem Streitpunkt zwischen den Großmagiern und ihrem besten Schüler.“
Vor seinem Ausschluss aus dem Tower äußerte das Konsortium seine Besorgnis über die möglichen verfälschenden Auswirkungen seiner Studien und versuchte...

...die Schrift auf der Seite ändert sich plötzlich und scheint die dokumentierte Geschichte zu verspotten. Auf der Seite tanzen Worte und Bilder, die einen inneren Verrat, eine Verschwörung eines verschlagenen Nekromanten und den Fall des Turms darstellen. Dann kam es zu einem Krieg zwischen den überlebenden Hochmagiern und einer Allianz aus Nekromanten und Todesrittern, angeführt von einem Dracolich, der das bösartige &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;Shroud de Aeternus Vitae&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt; trägt . Gesichter und Körper, ausgetrocknet von den dunklen Windungen des Dracolich, füllen die Seiten des unheiligen Buches. Schreie von einem längst vergessenen Schlachtfeld umgeben Sie und erreichen ein ohrenbetäubendes Crescendo. Du bist wie gelähmt, während dunkle Ranken aus den einzelnen Seiten des Buches herauskriechen ...

... dann verstummen Schreie aus dem Buch und die Ranken, die dich suchen, lösen sich auf. Worte tauchen auf, die die Geschichte eines dunklen Rituals erzählen, mit dem der Geist einer mächtigen Todesfee in einem lebenden Seelenkäfig gefangen gehalten werden soll. An den Rändern des Buches erscheinen feine Kritzeleien, die darauf hinweisen, dass Vorsicht geboten ist, damit der Nekromant nicht besessen wird.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4abe4ebag47f8g472cg987bg3f4160296b70" version="1">Die Seele einer kürzlich getöteten Kreatur weint vor Qual, als sie in einem &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Seelenschild&lt;/LSTag&gt; verschwindet.

Bietet +[1] für &lt;LSTag Tooltip= „ArmorClass“&gt;Rüstungsklasse&lt;/LSTag&gt; bis &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Lange Rast&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h192d0b65g8b34g4c7fg8f0dgbd2f3b6ee359" version="1">Die Seele einer kürzlich getöteten Kreatur schreit vor Wut, als sie im &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Seelenschild&lt;/LSTag&gt; verschwindet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Der Geist überlädt den Schild und liefert &lt;LSTag Tooltip ="Resistant"&gt;Resistenz&lt;/LSTag&gt; gegen physischen Schaden.

Alle Geisterbeschwörungen werden verstärkt und bieten zusätzliche Effekte.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8536ed01g1f71g45aagbeabg1fbe3d853dbb" version="1">Ein wirbelnder Geisterwirbel schützt den Nekromanten vor eingehenden Angriffen.

Hat +[1] auf &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Rüstungsklasse&lt;/LSTag&gt; bis &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Lange Rast&lt;/LSTag&gt;. [2] Zusätzliche Seele(n) können an den Seelenschild gebunden werden.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b44bc4cgeb9fg4a7fg9993g532c92f867e8" version="1">Ein wirbelnder Geisterwirbel schützt diesen &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Großen Untoten&lt;/LSTag&gt; vor eingehenden Angriffen.

Hat +[1] zu &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt; Rüstungsklasse&lt;/LSTag&gt; bis &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Lange Rast&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6a3624e0g9be7g4258g98ccge108bb196e15" version="1">Durch die Aktivierung von &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_DarkEmpathy" &gt;Dunkle Empathie&lt;/LSTag&gt; wird die Macht des Leichentuches auf deine Verbündeten ausgeweitet und sie erhalten [1] Heilung.</content>
  <content contentuid="h53162f10gd352g43b3gb3b3gbc1e547e5c86" version="1">Antiker Streitkolben</content>
  <content contentuid="h5953fb48g9283g4f79gad90g8d44e4dd2eb7" version="1">Andras der Teufelshund</content>
  <content contentuid="h49bb0ea9g617dg48dag8ae9gcc6fdf2609c9" version="1">As a cultist trained by the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_OrderOfTheDracolich"&gt;Order of the Dracolich&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you are &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; in Flails, Maces, Scimitars, Sickles, and Shields. You may call upon the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_DreadOverlord"&gt;Dread Overlord's&lt;/LSTag&gt; power to ignite your weapon with his dark fire with the cantrip &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_NecroticBlade"&gt;Necrotic Armaments&lt;/LSTag&gt; at-will.</content>
  <content contentuid="hffb1b1bbgb09bg45b2g93e9g26bb4df25a17" version="1">Der Aspekt des Schreckensherrschers</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c41d400g8095g41bfg9140g52cc987ae573" version="1">Aura of Despair</content>
  <content contentuid="he23d9d72g1eddg4d23g9ea1ge27b17a251da" version="1">Bind into a corpse the spirit of a powerful warlock under your command. This &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; has access to &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_UndeadPactMagic"&gt;Pact Magic&lt;/LSTag&gt; from your patron, allowing it to cast powerful spells and recharge its &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;Spell Slots&lt;/LSTag&gt; after each &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h585a9d60gedd1g4a91g85ecge67e416d436b" version="1">Bind the souls of fallen enemies to your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; adds +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You may reap the dead in the heat of battle.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a081293g4033g4d6dgbb39gec89f4e8b8ec" version="1">Bone Staff</content>
  <content contentuid="hb2f24e7fgafdag48eaga53bgcc0177c5d9d2" version="1">Brutal Leap</content>
  <content contentuid="h7bb77640ge20dg4d00gb017gf93846cd97c1" version="1">Call upon the Undying Emperor to aid you in battle! A fearsome aspect of the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_DreadOverlord"&gt;Dread Overlord&lt;/LSTag&gt; intervenes in your behalf.</content>
  <content contentuid="heaeb7d21g285fg4da6gb101gfc41d2243d2d" version="1">Captured Soul</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5702b8fg16c4g4f70ga122g2504a4754093" version="1">Captured Souls (Counter)</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9febc11gc208g4fc5g92e7g9de35add19d2" version="1">Command angry spirits from your soulshield to haunt your enemies. The &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; form into [1] shadow wraiths for [2] turns. The wraiths can use &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_ShadowStep"&gt;Shadow Teleportation&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Inkblot"&gt;Darkness Cloak&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Shadow wraiths have &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="HASTE"&gt;Haste&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hea24c6d1g8b45g410bga050g0ad95dfea456" version="1">Command angry spirits from your soulshield to haunt your enemies. The &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; form into [1] shadow wraiths for [2] turns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Shadow wraiths have &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="HASTE"&gt;Haste&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d1db98bge1fbg406cg9e2dg5ffcdb58def2" version="1">Commit Corpse</content>
  <content contentuid="hb966a654g429dg4fcdgadccg78c1ad89da24" version="1">Consume Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="ha7e2a15eg4904g4768gba23g06c86072f825" version="1">Corrupted by the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_DreadOverlord"&gt;Dread Overlord's&lt;/LSTag&gt; cruelty, malice and will to dominate all life, the cultists of the &lt;i&gt;Order of the Dracolich&lt;/i&gt; carry out his terror on Toril. In return for their service, the dracolich promised dominion over life and death itself with many cultists believing that with enough power you can overcome both. Wielding armies of undead, they devote their lives and unlives to the mastery over mortality. Their battlecry 'MORS PRINCIPIUM EST!' is in defiance over the very concept of finality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; -- Excerpt from the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h15bb4a25gc64eg43dbg8b25ge65d2be206fc" version="1">Create a skeletal giant under your command. A massive frontline attacker, this &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; strikes with &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_GiantSlam_Passive"&gt;phenomenal power&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Once per turn, the skeletal giant can slam its weapon into enemies in a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_SkeletalGiant_Slam"&gt;Gargantuan Strike&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h67a93f42gcc22g4b19gbf33g209068ac46fc" version="1">Cries of terror fill the air as souls of the dead swirl around.</content>
  <content contentuid="h366b9497ga100g484agb6d6ge5f161d603cd" version="1">Cursed to rise again as an undead under the service of the Dread Overlord.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8120574ag158cg46a4g9655g8c3a974b5c20" version="1">Cuts and wounds close up on this creature's body as rivulets of vitality is stripped from nearby enemies by a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;vampiric shroud&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc16e300g2cbag4308ga25cg62f18560e98c" version="1">Dark coils emanating from a nearby &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;Shroud de Aeternus Vitae&lt;/LSTag&gt; swirls around in a soothing embrace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This creature will receive half of [1] per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc51e3a40g7924g4fdcg916cg7bef6a571cf6" version="1">Dunkle Empathie</content>
  <content contentuid="h18fc3583gd0b4g4141g9664g931f01ebe02f" version="1">Dunkle Empathie</content>
  <content contentuid="h302e58e4g65d3g4de3gb3e7g86197b93df42" version="1">Dark tendrils pour forth ominously from this creature's vampiric &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;Shroud de Aeternus Vitae&lt;/LSTag&gt; in ravenous search of life.</content>
  <content contentuid="h06d03102g68e7g481cg9602g67733b4d9e52" version="1">Desecrated Corpse</content>
  <content contentuid="h45baf224gfd30g4c98g8ea1g0a36a134b701" version="1">Schreckenskultist</content>
  <content contentuid="h347a4b46g874dg40f3g8df2gb2650cceed82" version="1">Dread Ward</content>
  <content contentuid="ha04bac6ag5b46g417bg8ec0g772e730ee1a0" version="1">Empowered Soulshield</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a6725a2g5fd8g4a2eg80b9g706052d334df" version="1">Ensnare the souls of recently slain enemies into your ravenous soulshield. Triggers automatically at the end of each combat round as long as concentration is maintained.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6bb6e110gf7ceg4556g8807g412f055f9065" version="1">Ensnared Soul</content>
  <content contentuid="he6b60600g9048g4090gb48fgbcf4678c9ef2" version="1">Eternal Servitude</content>
  <content contentuid="h7aed3dc3g252eg4b85gaf81gb89f71da4de2" version="1">Fear Incarnate</content>
  <content contentuid="hb4123dd5g52eeg41ceg8a0bg59e9facb2a20" version="1">Feeding</content>
  <content contentuid="h0cf889a0g74ccg44b5ga5a3g3d69641c98a7" version="1">Fell power corrupted this artifact and laid claim to its necromancy in its unholy name.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a2834c9g2b40g4328g90dfg281b22ebb8eb" version="1">Fell power has laid claim to the Forbidden Knowledge in the Necromancy of Thay and corrupted it in its unholy name. The book's dark secrets are fully revealed to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_SoulMagnet"&gt;Soul Magnet&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you know the spells &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_CursedTome_CurriculumofStrategy"&gt;Curriculum of Strategy: Artistry of War&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_CursedTome_Dethrone"&gt;Dethrone&lt;/LSTag&gt;, both of which you may cast without expending &lt;LSTag Tooltip="WarlockSpellSlot"&gt;Warlock Spell Slots&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9320ba1cg29b8g4efeg8071gb27c20197854" version="1">Fell power has laid claim to the Forbidden Knowledge in the Necromancy of Thay and corrupted it in its unholy name.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You learned of a dark ritual to turn yourself into a living &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_SoulMagnet"&gt;Soul Magnet&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h42a73650g1be7g4883g9cbfg3ca954d76b75" version="1">Fell power has laid claim to the necromancy in the armor Reaper's Embrace and corrupted it in its unholy name. Your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; is no longer restricted while wearing Reaper's Embrace when wearing Light, Medium, or Heavy Armor in any slot including gloves, boots, and helmets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are also &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; in Medium and Heavy Armor while wearing Reaper's Embrace.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d4cf372g2075g403dg98b5g44c22b9b4227" version="1">Find Familiar: Devil Dog</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bb43152g923eg4d2aga8edg096b745342c8" version="1">Flaming Apparition</content>
  <content contentuid="h20eb14dagd9c0g431egb33eg6c721ddc0017" version="1">Forbidden Lore</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a87d574g5350g41c4g847fg5ae1b5f508cc" version="1">Forbidden Lore: Libor Mortis</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d2cd1b8gd001g49a5g8bebgdb7db0079ab1" version="1">Forbidden Lore: Order of the Dracolich</content>
  <content contentuid="h603073ccgd75cg4282g8b0eg1c855a5d7e67" version="1">Forbidden Lore: Shroud of Eternal Life</content>
  <content contentuid="he8b382d5ga329g47bbgb57cg2468bc3402fe" version="1">Forbidden Lore: Soul Harvest</content>
  <content contentuid="h8665d9fbgd223g4fe5gb90egfe89305f5789" version="1">Forbidden Lore: The Greater Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1977291g4151g4d7fga9a0gb3f3cf190d20" version="1">Forbidden Lore: The Undying Emperor</content>
  <content contentuid="h00e35c4ag34aeg4410g81f0g12e5d5730453" version="1">Gain +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; (+[2] with &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_Soulshield_Improved"&gt;Improved Soul Harvest&lt;/LSTag&gt; and +[3] with &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_Soulshield_Greater"&gt;Greater Soul Harvest&lt;/LSTag&gt;) until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Bind additional souls to your soulshield with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul"&gt;Commit Corpse&lt;/LSTag&gt;, which adds +[4] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; per additional soul.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvesting souls beyond the current capacity of your soulshield overcharges it granting increased &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all physical damage for a short time. It will also result in an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL_MAX"&gt;Empowered Soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt; granting additional effects to your spirit invocations.</content>
  <content contentuid="heba6f8e8ge669g4207ga9e6g13103504522d" version="1">Gain the power of life and death by imbuing yourself with the abilities of the undead - of vampires, wraiths, and banshees - through an unholy &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;Shroud of Eternal Life&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_Aeternusvitae"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4d06997g1c46g4fb8gaea6g648b37d242af" version="1">Gargantuan Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e9b1975g9ebdg4d04gaeb2ge216d83a829f" version="1">Ghostly Apparition</content>
  <content contentuid="h853788ebg4763g40d4g82ecg27c7b51f3a08" version="1">Ghostly Apparition</content>
  <content contentuid="h485476f1g39a8g4e85g9723g0015af0ee770" version="1">Ghostly Apparitions</content>
  <content contentuid="h6ae3ed26gb73dg4d11g9dbcgf5289c0e3d17" version="1">Ghostly apparitions surround this entity providing protection. Affected entity has +[1] to their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbfc92d93g6389g4b30g9e91gfa39b171c7aa" version="1">Glaring Threat</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6942834g139eg4beegaef6g98d060c41ee0" version="1">Greater Shield of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h0d05f79fgced6g48b7g8d77gc17dc62c2732" version="1">Greater Shield of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h06360aa9g5762g4fdeg8094g9db05ee6ebb6" version="1">Greater Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="h851fae46ga4c1g4d1bgbf28g7528e989c9cf" version="1">Harvesting souls beyond the current capacity of your soulshield overcharges it granting increased &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all physical damage for a short time. It will also result in an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL_MAX"&gt;Empowered Soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt; granting additional effects to your spirit invocations.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e5fe951g6788g49fdga560g91fa4f1fc97a" version="1">Hide Shroud</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2686facg4ffcg40ecg8f6dg58395e85bbf9" version="1">Ignite your weapon with the Undying Emperor's dark fire for a short time, dealing an additional [1]. Your imbued weapon cannot be disarmed by enemies. Flails, maces, scimitars, and sickles wielded offhand are also ignited.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f1cc620g2ec5g4facga963gafcf01783dc8" version="1">Improved Shield of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h961cb081ga713g4ca7g98b0g58204f968e53" version="1">In return for its service after death, this &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; has access to Pact Magic from the necromancer's patron, allowing it to cast spells. It has two Level 2 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;Spell Slots&lt;/LSTag&gt; which recharges after every &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha8da330fgac69g4ffdgbb20g2bdd768a4cde" version="1">Infernal Skeletal Hound and a Good Boy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd35a5c51g2c73g42b8ga8d8g18ebffee8700" version="1">Inflict Curse</content>
  <content contentuid="hde21d834g66e1g4b2cgb2e5g7073fe82de8a" version="1">Invoke Spirit: Apparition</content>
  <content contentuid="h607087acg8d65g4141ga1e6g13cc80b2516e" version="1">Invoke Spirit: Haunt</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bfa83d1g1928g4622g9b77gd6772beed12b" version="1">Invoke Spirit: Phantasm</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc030ee1gaa10g4edaga077gc40b52b7c756" version="1">Invoke Spirit: Poltergeist</content>
  <content contentuid="hbdfe7049gf204g4e41g92c9g3d8d52fe3037" version="1">Invoke Spirit: Spook</content>
  <content contentuid="hdf8424c9g4ed7g4ea0g8feegdc7f3a69a135" version="1">Invoker of Spirits: Greater Soul Harvest</content>
  <content contentuid="h312fca1ag37b8g482eg922eg5734fdb94adc" version="1">Invoker of Spirits: Improved Soul Harvest</content>
  <content contentuid="h60be2d0dg1ea2g495cg94fbgd33e5ae431da" version="1">Invoker of Spirits: Soul Harvest</content>
  <content contentuid="h949924cfg70d6g4f27g82b7g51775e57913b" version="1">Leap into enemies. Your sheer size knocks creatures &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h49043818gbe86g4bf9g9cc7g8ba3ed9e3861" version="1">Life Drained</content>
  <content contentuid="h0d2bcf2aga493g4fccg8fefgc67fc14df568" version="1">Minion Points</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbd916e8g729fg4ebbg804dg181d2412378b" version="1">Minion Points (Counter)</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9474babg6bd4g4e00gb39fg72231630d280" version="1">Monolith of Terror</content>
  <content contentuid="h1cb04f42gb3d9g4947g8229ge29d46396384" version="1">Murder of Crows</content>
  <content contentuid="had1b2c78gbf90g4871gb3b2g8d9cf64e1fdd" version="1">Necrotic Armaments</content>
  <content contentuid="h1500da70gd0f0g4e45gb93eg204d3007ef7d" version="1">Necrotic Armaments (Savage Attacker)</content>
  <content contentuid="h0d78cbadg02a6g493ag9ceeg939a9be4d318" version="1">Necrotic Energies</content>
  <content contentuid="h09575007g0455g44c4g902cg75c4a7ad4d16" version="1">Necrotic Fists</content>
  <content contentuid="he8217cf2g2af8g4792g8a5cg1b6610541828" version="1">Necrotic powers fills this creature with unholy vigor, bestowing upon them resistances to physical weapon and necrotic damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c26cb4ag4c51g4f00gbd20ga726c386fce3" version="1">Necrotic Shillelagh</content>
  <content contentuid="ha560e8b1g749eg4c41g97a4gcc748594d71d" version="1">Night of the Living Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d7f6429gcb97g494fga886gca5de7173f5d" version="1">Pact of Eternal Life</content>
  <content contentuid="h30fe1de9g865eg4867gb296gde147c326eb4" version="1">Perform a ritual to bind the soul of a slain being to your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; adds +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h50423c57g13d5g4068ga8edgda2b1dfd4b5b" version="1">Profane Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="h55de4b20gf507g4399gab7dg17765dc4d667" version="1">Profane Blessing: Corrupted Armor</content>
  <content contentuid="hcff8cfeag4194g44f6g9237g8b81bd139695" version="1">Profane Blessing: Corrupted Armor</content>
  <content contentuid="hb244d7b0ga6e8g44fagb47cgd612b128022b" version="1">Profane Blessing: Corrupted Grimoire</content>
  <content contentuid="he0b657fdg2578g4a2agb38bg99d757dd91fa" version="1">Profane Intervention</content>
  <content contentuid="hf983fe3eg4898g4f88g96dbg742af32860fe" version="1">Profane Intervention: Aspect of the Dread Overlord</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b4bd924gb7bcg49f9gb525g039e608de8c5" version="1">Profane Possession</content>
  <content contentuid="h8130b0b3g6040g4e21g98afg9b0c0838e85b" version="1">Read the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt; by activating its tooltip.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha99a681fg0034g482egb2d9g6a80a285ded8" version="1">Reap the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bca2a76gb189g4c5cga160ge0bd908c783a" version="1">Reap the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="hb2f93f7eg989ag48d0g94b4gf0ef50411b1e" version="1">Recharging</content>
  <content contentuid="heef45ae5g4557g4704gab7agba6910d85d29" version="1">Reclaim Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="h0440aeebgefa7g466dgbc9eg8fa5e079ba80" version="1">Release a spirit from your soulshield to distract your enemies, allowing you to retreat to safety without spending any &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ActionPoint"&gt;action&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="BonusActionPoint"&gt;bonus action&lt;/LSTag&gt;. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Your movement is &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DASH"&gt;doubled&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h95d3d3bdg405bg4f68g82b6g7ba27f60a7f5" version="1">Release spirits from your soulshield to distract your enemies, allowing you to retreat to safety without spending any &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ActionPoint"&gt;action&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="BonusActionPoint"&gt;bonus action&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Nearby enemies can be &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt; if they fail a Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Affected enemies are &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SLOW"&gt;slowed&lt;/LSTag&gt; and your movement is &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DASH"&gt;doubled&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h316c0919g0a40g42a2g931egd93bacac98db" version="1">Release troublesome spirits from your soulshield to harass your enemies, moving objects and shoving creatures [1] away from you. Their mischief &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DAZED"&gt;dazes&lt;/LSTag&gt; enemies on a failed Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; The poltergeists lash out in anger, dealing [2] or half that if targets succeed on their Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h84ef9b64g0775g4fa7g8e56g213e3adde5a8" version="1">Release troublesome spirits from your soulshield to harass your enemies, moving objects and shoving creatures [1] away from you. Their mischief knocks enemies &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt; on a failed Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; The poltergeists lash out in anger, dealing [2] or half that if targets succeed on their Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h14e36a58g71c0g4e7dgbcf1gf069bc9552a5" version="1">Retract the dark tendrils emanating from your vampiric shroud.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1838b20egbb78g4678gbd2ag92971a82d2c2" version="1">Screaming Spirit</content>
  <content contentuid="hf6a6c24dg8f9cg44f4g8f7cge17248e68937" version="1">Screaming Spirits</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc33c2f8g2f25g43bagb138g1da300081ddb" version="1">Screaming Spirits</content>
  <content contentuid="h2cc78a0bg9c6ag4a5dga79dg3af38c13100d" version="1">Sever the link to the undead created by the curse &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Regain a &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_MINIONPOINTS"&gt;Minion Point&lt;/LSTag&gt; per each reclaimed undead.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d3764e8g9957g4035gbe02g1871e2a7e99a" version="1">Shadow Beast</content>
  <content contentuid="haf4a9d68gf416g4350gb933gab7f71427545" version="1">Shield of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h539a7efcg6a41g42abga596g59d44e563c0e" version="1">Shield of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h7764ff44ga22fg423dg8563g640fb7f59f67" version="1">Shroud de Aeternus Vitae</content>
  <content contentuid="hc73709abg4a67g4acagb35dga33dffc731a6" version="1">Skeletal Giant</content>
  <content contentuid="he246e995g80b8g4564g819ag4836157d20fd" version="1">Skeletal Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="ha786d31bg56d0g4bccg910dgf268fce23bc2" version="1">Slam the massive weapon into enemies with unbridled force, creating a small shockwave centered on the target and knocking all creatures &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5e2cb69gf43ag4bcdgb66cg04514deb9c0e" version="1">Some consider the raising of the Greater Undead as sacrilege. None can question the pure devastation a giant or a powerful warlock can cause while alive, but worse still when coupled with the unholy powers of necromancy. Warlocks who have failed to achieve lichdom or prevent their deaths have entered their names into the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt; in hopes that their damned souls will be returned into material plane in a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Animate_SkeletalMage"&gt;semblance of unlife&lt;/LSTag&gt; by a worthy necromancer. Only an evil warlock would willingly allow themselves to be raised in such a way. Luckily, the power necessary to raise such undead is within the means of only a few...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; -- Excerpt from the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;...What follows are scribbles of incantations and pleas to ancient and long-forgotten gods of death and necromancy deities from planes and worlds from beyond Toril. Their names don't ring familiar to you - Vrall, Savoy, Enigma, Thy - but you sense unholy power behind them in the incantations.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe89420bg47c7g4630g8110ge15bafec1bf3" version="1">Soul Magnet</content>
  <content contentuid="ha25b00c9g3d84g44ffgb3e2g71aafa279d34" version="1">Soul Magnet: Harvest Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e40b7a0g75b6g47d0g9c23g3ad347f4c8b2" version="1">Souls of recently slain creatures cry in torment as they disappear into a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each captured soul provides +[1] to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;. The soulshield may hold at the maximum up to [2] additional souls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have captured souls equal to the turns remaining.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1c0afcdag61d4g4becga9acg972e425b3417" version="1">Souls of the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a14ea99g3b2dg48c2gadf0g0dde8528a6cc" version="1">Souls of the dead scream in anguish around this creature before succumbing to its &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h529699edg641dg49d1g904ag8819787ecedf" version="1">Suffuse your necrotic attacks with a curse capable of binding the living to an unlife of service upon dying.&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;Toggle on to allow your cantrips, spells, and weapon attacks to apply &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Limited by your current &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_MINIONPOINTS"&gt;Minion Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3da3775cgff70g445cgba05g61bd80bd06cd" version="1">Summon a familiar with the form of an infernal skeletal hound with a &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="BrutalBite"&gt;brutal bite&lt;/LSTag&gt; and a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Terrifying_Howl"&gt;terrifying howl&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Warning: may sometimes eat crayons!</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cf8d405g6f68g4e77g9e4fgb8225f2bc2e8" version="1">Summon lost souls from the grave and form them into a protective shield around you. Binding additional souls to your soulshield confer increased protection and unlocks the ability to invoke the spirits to do your bidding, whether for good or for malintent.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b0d7986g5219g47fcga1a2g910d40169806" version="1">Summoner of the Damned</content>
  <content contentuid="h13b7eb70g93e2g4de6g87caga7c0ae82bf41" version="1">Summoner of the Damned: Create Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="ha344d145g11a1g415bga8c9g9e4c407a4488" version="1">Summoner of the Damned: Skeletal Giant</content>
  <content contentuid="h1094aa64gac98g47ddgb882g665a20c4564e" version="1">Summoner of the Damned: Skeletal Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h375b31fcg73c7g4d13g9defg09a415a1d372" version="1">The air around you grows chill and suddenly you feel your patron's presence. Your mind darkens as the world melts away save for a grotesque tome revealing its profane knowledge to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d3d3b85gac1cg437egb3b4g2497ce1a307c" version="1">The air around you grows chill and suddenly you feel your patron's presence. Your mind darkens as the world melts away save for a grotesque tome revealing its profane knowledge to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="h5839c93bg660fg4965g89d6g1fd88c4749cb" version="1">The air around you grows chill and suddenly you feel your patron's presence. Your mind darkens as the world melts away save for a grotesque tome revealing its profane knowledge to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="h168224a6g659eg4810gab6agcfb76aaa0a82" version="1">The air around you grows chill and suddenly you feel your patron's presence. Your mind darkens as the world melts away save for a grotesque tome revealing its profane knowledge to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5f25e16gc772g41e0g9d32gf0095a2cfa00" version="1">The aspect can &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_AspectOfTheDreadOverlord_ConsumeSouls"&gt;Consume Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; of your foes in a large area and damages itself each turn until it is spent. The aspect's attacks curse your enemies with &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;, binding them into service as one of the undead upon dying.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the aspect persists, its presence provides a &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ASPECTOFTHEDREADOVERLORD_PRESENCE_BUFF"&gt;Dread Ward&lt;/LSTag&gt; that protects you and your allies while imposing an oppressive &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ASPECTOFTHEDREADOVERLORD_PRESENCE_TERROR"&gt;Aura of Despair&lt;/LSTag&gt; against your enemies.</content>
  <content contentuid="h47031131gb56fg4fd6g9580gb07f9e4a13cf" version="1">The dark energies from this creature's &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_NecroticBlade"&gt;Necrotic Armaments&lt;/LSTag&gt; fills them with &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_UnholyVigor"&gt;Unholy Vigor&lt;/LSTag&gt;. They are &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to[1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h20617334gfa90g4125ga994gee30a262f8eb" version="1">The dark fire from your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_NecroticBlade"&gt;Necrotic Armaments&lt;/LSTag&gt; adds its damage to your unarmed attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8ad6ae5g6894g43fdg90c7gf7dee6dfd97b" version="1">Die dunklen Ranken, die von deinem &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;Shroud de Aeternus Vitae&lt;/LSTag&gt; ausgehen, sind auf das Leben um dich herum eingestimmt. Du kannst diese dunkle Empathie aktivieren, um die Reichweite des vampirischen Leichentuchs zu erhöhen und die Hälfte der Lebenskraft, die es abzieht, mit Verbündeten in der Nähe zu teilen. Wenn der Effekt endet, dauert es einige Zeit, bis sich dein Leichentuch erholt.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3258eadegb8c8g47aegb570gf595985ffae7" version="1">The dracolich's oppressive aura gives the affected entity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt; while within [1] of the aspect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5be8a9a1g3e09g49c5gbb4ag9efe3ba9b246" version="1">The Dread Overlord</content>
  <content contentuid="hfefe00f0g3849g40b9g8dadg66ffb9100090" version="1">The Necromancy of Thay has taught you how to transform your body into a ravenous &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_SOULMAGNET"&gt;Vortex of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; to ensnare spirits of enemies recently killed in battle, binding them to your soulshield at the end of each combat round.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b0a060dg685fg4c9fga5d1gf9887bff8748" version="1">The Skeletal Warlock can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_ChillTouch"&gt;Chill Touch&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_RayOfSickness_2"&gt;Ray of Sickness&lt;/LSTag&gt; at will. It can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_RayOfEnfeeblement"&gt;Ray of Enfeeblement&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_ScorchingRay"&gt;Scorching Ray&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Sleep_2"&gt;Sleep&lt;/LSTag&gt; as 2nd-level spells using its two Level 2 spell slots. It can afflict enemies with &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt; with its necrotic attacks. It gains the ability to cast the spells &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Slow"&gt;Slow&lt;/LSTag&gt; at class level 8 and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DeathWard"&gt;Death Ward&lt;/LSTag&gt; at class level 11 once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd85a75b0g6b9cg4b5dg9ef1gb2336934459c" version="1">The soul of a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Animate_SkeletalMage"&gt;powerful warlock&lt;/LSTag&gt; has been bound to this corpse to serve a dark design.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6830189g9dc7g411fga5fdg7253d93de590" version="1">The souls of dead form a formidable shield of protection as they spiral around this creature wailing in agony.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has +[1] to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5e8137bfge898g4e80g906eg18ba8b63c70c" version="1">The very air writhes in dread at the dracolich's malevolent presence. The putrid stench of death and decay surrounds him like a malignant shroud.</content>
  <content contentuid="he3e5adb1g1566g451bgaa39g633dfd57808e" version="1">This &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; strikes with phenomenal power! It knocks nearby creatures &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt; every time it lands a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="CriticalHit"&gt;Critical Hit&lt;/LSTag&gt; or a killing blow.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf83b4a95gcddag475fga40dg74b89f127677" version="1">This corpse has been defiled by a foul ritual.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b643d6fg72c1g4581ga4d7gdc945237651b" version="1">This creature is being drained by a nearby &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;vampiric aura&lt;/LSTag&gt;, receiving [1] per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h479ed4afgd363g4552g8a72g074704f82b32" version="1">This creature swells with &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_UnholyVigor"&gt;Unholy Vigor&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to[1] and all of its attacks deal additional [2].</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd6c7110g3394g4455g9dfdg6b4afad3a7a1" version="1">This creature's soul is in danger of being ensared by a nearby &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_SOULMAGNET"&gt;Vortex of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt; upon dying.</content>
  <content contentuid="hef7faab5g788eg42f7g97a7g32711bed66bb" version="1">This massive weapon is taller than a humanoid. Rust covers the metallic surface, speaking to its age.</content>
  <content contentuid="h90fba306gc25fg459bgb354g3c2b80e4b0f4" version="1">This necromancer's weapon attacks burn with dark fire, dealing extra[1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f71142egb8b1g4a4fg83ceg3637473de325" version="1">This powerful &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="Undead"&gt;undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; is &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; from the effects of &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_ControlUndead"&gt;Control Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; and has &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="TurnResistance"&gt;Turn Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="MagicResistance"&gt;Magic&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha9d6743dgdbccg4e59gaedcgcd9c385a3c24" version="1">This undead's attacks blaze with dark fire, dealing extra[1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hfee3b224g75e1g40c3g9c4ag34b9e3593af7" version="1">This weapon blazes with your dracolich patron's fire, dealing extra[1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h458bd54fg1bfag40b1g9b0eg1deba17f01d7" version="1">Toggle off to silence the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_SOULSHIELD_EFFECT"&gt;Screaming Spirits&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7320f7e4g5b8cg40f1gb6eegf1474ed7d70e" version="1">Unholy Vigor</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8eb0b7eg2d5dg4239g8d9fgaf24e3267fff" version="1">Unholy Vigor</content>
  <content contentuid="h8214ad5eg3ec0g4557g9d30g6d0f3cc45016" version="1">Unholy Vigor</content>
  <content contentuid="h655ce86dgfb82g4aa1g9540g5daf79483fe1" version="1">Unholy Vigor: Resistance to Necrotic Damage</content>
  <content contentuid="he9663250gea85g4554gaa67gf49555cfddb7" version="1">Unleash a wave of death and rip the souls from these puny mortals! Afflicts enemies with &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;, a curse that binds them to service as one of the undead upon dying.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8143ea25ge101g42f7gab17gb7f0d3907c0c" version="1">Vampiric Shroud</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ac2db1fgf12fg4219g8b1bg08a47eb466e1" version="1">Vortex of Souls</content>
  <content contentuid="h053ccc0cg61e8g4c85g9e21g71fd7be06ca3" version="1">When making a melee weapon attack, you roll your damage dice twice and use the highest result.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d41e35cg1d82g4b6agb3c7ge26090d4fd9e" version="1">Whispers from legions of the dead and undead emanate from the object, barely audible yet as loud and raucous as thunder in your mind, beseeching your patron in his many names.</content>
  <content contentuid="h004d7f42g80cfg49c9g8527g966a4f21e77b" version="1">Whispers, barely audible at first, darken your mind becoming louder and more insistent. You feel the presence of your patron as the world dissolves around you save for a leather-bound book. A chill overtakes you as your eyes flit across the words on the cover - &lt;i&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/i&gt;. Its pages open revealing its secrets to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5366f40g4a16g4a26gb6e2g760fe52ad0df" version="1">Wield a vampiric shroud that absorbs the vitality of nearby living enemies. Its dark tendrils inflict [1] to enemies and heal you for [2] per turn. The shroud persists until your next &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Affected enemies caught inside the shroud continually &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;bleed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h16662000gbb3cg49e1gadc7g059c55625b87" version="1">Will [2] ghostly phantasms from your soulshield to strike your foes, each dealing [1] on a hit. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Doubles the damage of each Phantasm.</content>
  <content contentuid="h562f770fg083ag4e9fgaecbg0436c24b1c19" version="1">Will a ghostly phantasm from your soulshield to strike a target of your choosing, dealing [1] on a hit. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Doubles the damage of each Phantasm.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd0883a3gbb36g4a52g9190g415643ec5498" version="1">Wrath of the Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b1c55e1gaf4bg408dg9540ge1f1e01bbc2f" version="1">Wrench the very souls from the mortal husks of your weakened enemies and bind them to your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Executes enemies with less than 20% health. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; adds +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8540e2e2ga727g4072gad88g4ae08e7ac8ea" version="1">You are &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistant&lt;/LSTag&gt; to[1].&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imbuing your weapon with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_NecroticBlade"&gt;Necrotic Armaments&lt;/LSTag&gt; fills you Unholy Vigor, making you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to[1] for a short time.</content>
  <content contentuid="h31726191g9b43g4636ga931g2e7e9cccc4be" version="1">You are surrounded by a swirling vortex of lost and phantom spirits screaming in terror as you bind them to your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4dd8afa8g1f8fg4644g9a3bged1e15764c35" version="1">You have full control of the soulshield when wearing any armor in any slots while wearing Reaper's Embrace.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfbb4b032g3fd3g4bebg9521g1540908e93a8" version="1">You invoke his name - &lt;i&gt;Dread Overlord&lt;/i&gt; - and suddenly you feel his presence. Your mind darkens as the world melts away save for a grotesque tome opening its pages to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="h6a9d4eeagd88dg40a6g9281g5e5131c346c4" version="1">You know the spell &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_AnimateDead"&gt;Animate Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt; which you may cast at-will. You also gain the power to create &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; such as a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Animate_SkeletalMage"&gt;Skeletal Warlock&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="WarlockSpellSlot"&gt;Warlock Spell Slot&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may summon each type of &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; in addition to a minor undead from the spell &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_AnimateDead"&gt;Animate Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_GreaterUndead"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h386e50e9g7a5dg472bgaed2ge8a3919f7d14" version="1">You know the spell &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_CreateUndead"&gt;Create Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt;, allowing you to raise a fearsome mummy at-will. This does not count towards spells gained from the Mystic Arcanum feature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9617b74dge713g455bg8ba2gbc936fe8b460" version="1">You may command a spirit from your soulshield to come to the aid of an ally as a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ReactionActionPoint"&gt;reaction&lt;/LSTag&gt;, adding +2 to their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Reduces all incoming damage by 1.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8cd6fc39g9e52g4654gbfb1g600b17a12d7a" version="1">You may command spirits from your soulshield to come to the aid of an ally as a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ReactionActionPoint"&gt;reaction&lt;/LSTag&gt;, adding +[1] to their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns. This consumes the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Empowered Soulshield:&lt;/i&gt; Reduces all incoming damage by [2].</content>
  <content contentuid="hfba2c00age847g47a8g89bbg282f0cd2402b" version="1">You may harvest souls of the dead and bind them in a greater soulshield for protection or invoke the spirits' wrath against your enemies. You can command the souls of the dead to surround you in a protective &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, initially adding +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may bind additional spirits to your soulshield from corpses with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul"&gt;Commit Corpse&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul_Reap"&gt;Reap the Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or rip the souls of nearly dead enemies with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul_Dying"&gt;Reap the Dying&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; provides an additional +[2] to Armor Class.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Invoke the spirits with greater &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Spook_Greater"&gt;Spook&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Apparition_Greater"&gt;Apparition&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_DreadOverlord_SoulSpear_Greater"&gt;Phantasm&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Haunt_Greater"&gt;Haunt&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Zone_DreadOverlord_Poltergeist_Greater"&gt;Poltergeist&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvesting souls beyond the current capacity of your soulshield overcharges it granting increased &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all physical damage for a short time. It will also result in an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL_MAX"&gt;Empowered Soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt; granting additional effects to your spirit invocations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_SoulHarvest"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e2a1c86ga2deg4cf2gbca6gee5e4d3c1235" version="1">You may harvest souls of the dead and bind them in a soulshield for protection or invoke the spirits' wrath against your enemies. You can command the souls of the dead to surround you in a protective &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, initially adding +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may bind additional spirits to your soulshield with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul"&gt;Commit Corpse&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; provides an additional +[2] to Armor Class.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may command the captured soul to do your bidding in combat. As long as you have a &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; available, you may invoke the spirit to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Spook"&gt;Spook&lt;/LSTag&gt; your enemies, protect an ally through a ghostly &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Apparition"&gt;Apparition&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or will the vengeful &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_DreadOverlord_SoulSpear"&gt;Phantasm&lt;/LSTag&gt; to strike your enemies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvesting souls beyond the current capacity of your soulshield overcharges it granting increased &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all physical damage for a short time. It will also result in an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL_MAX"&gt;Empowered Soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt; granting additional effects to your spirit invocations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_SoulHarvest"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha192c400gd4d4g4ac8ga589gd6ae2ed5c4fb" version="1">You may harvest souls of the dead and bind them in an improved soulshield for protection or invoke the spirits' wrath against your enemies. You can command the souls of the dead to surround you in a protective &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Soulshield"&gt;Shield of Souls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, initially adding +[1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmorClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; until &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may bind additional spirits to your soulshield from corpses with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul"&gt;Commit Corpse&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_HarvestSoul_Reap"&gt;Reap the Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Each &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL"&gt;Captured Soul&lt;/LSTag&gt; provides an additional +[2] to Armor Class.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your command of the souls of the dead has grown in power: you may invoke the spirits with improved versions of &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_Spook_Improved"&gt;Spook&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Apparition_Improved"&gt;Apparition&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_DreadOverlord_SoulSpear_Improved"&gt;Phantasm&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You may also invoke the spirits to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Haunt"&gt;Haunt&lt;/LSTag&gt; an enemy or enlist a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Zone_DreadOverlord_Poltergeist"&gt;Poltergeist&lt;/LSTag&gt; to push enemies away.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvesting souls beyond the current capacity of your soulshield overcharges it granting increased &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistances&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all physical damage for a short time. It will also result in an &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DREADOVERLORD_HARVESTED_SOUL_MAX"&gt;Empowered Soulshield&lt;/LSTag&gt; granting additional effects to your spirit invocations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_SoulHarvest"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45cb10bbg9fb7g4b5agbeb0g15556fa69984" version="1">You may raise undead from the curse &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to the remaining duration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bd29efdg2b84g4463g8a18g829d62439d09" version="1">You're a cultist fighting under the banner of the Dread Overlord, a monstrous dracolich necromancer who seeks to spread His maleficence and terror over all lands. In return for your service, boundless power over death itself and the promise of eternal life await. Command the very souls of the dead and raise powerful Greater Undead in His profane name!</content>
  <content contentuid="h4fe2983ag262cg45d4gab85g93dacfd70523" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_UnholyVigor"&gt;Unholy Vigor&lt;/LSTag&gt; makes you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to[1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h2df178c1gb5e5g437agb3fagda04452e2fc9" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_UnholyVigor"&gt;Unholy Vigor&lt;/LSTag&gt; makes you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistant&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Necrotic damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h979a986egdef5g400dgb131g1631af707565" version="1">Your ability to inflict &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Night of the Living Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt; is limited by your current Minion Points.&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;Replenished by &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63d58aafg2808g4020g8415g4aa42cd9e0c0" version="1">Dein Pakt mit dem &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_DreadOverlord"&gt;Schreckensherrscher&lt;/LSTag&gt; hat dich mit profanem Wissen verflucht. Addiere +1 zu jedem Wurf, der entweder mit &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Arcana"&gt;Arcana&lt;/LSTag&gt; oder &lt;LSTag Tooltip="History"&gt;History&lt;/LSTag&gt; erstellt wurde.

Die grausame Überlieferung hat dir beigebracht, wie du Feinde, die durch nekrotischen Schaden durch deine Cantrips, Zaubersprüche und Waffenangriffe geschädigt wurden, mit &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="NIGHTOFTHELIVINGDEAD"&gt;Nacht der lebenden Toten&lt;/LSTag&gt; verfluchen und sie zum Untod verurteilen kannst .

Außerdem kannst du auf magische Weise auf den &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zugreifen, um seine unheiligen Seiten zu sehen.

</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ba64c76g8f11g4913gb50ag83ae01e1d6e4" version="1">Euer Schutzherr ist der Schreckensherrscher, ein monströser drakolischer Nekromant, der seine Boshaftigkeit und seinen Schrecken über alle Länder verbreiten will.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0cfe606bg1287g46a9g9dedg03d3013048c9" version="1">Your power to command the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; grows. You can now raise a terrifying &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DreadOverlord_Animate_SkeletalGiant"&gt;Skeletal Giant&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="WarlockSpellSlot"&gt;Warlock Spell Slot&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may summon each type of &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_ImmuneToControlUndead"&gt;Greater Undead&lt;/LSTag&gt; in addition to a minor undead from the spell &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_AnimateDead"&gt;Animate Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excerpt regarding &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_GreaterUndead"&gt;this necromantic power&lt;/LSTag&gt; reveals itself in the &lt;i&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="DreadOverlord_LORE_LiborMortis"&gt;Libor Mortis&lt;/LSTag&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9eb37bfg5e10g442cg86e3g5c0d45f37b6b" version="1">Your recent attempts to empathize with your allies has left you drained. Your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DreadOverlord_ShroudDeAeternusVitae"&gt;vampiric shroud&lt;/LSTag&gt; is currently recharging.</content>
</contentList>