<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>

	<content contentuid="83e224ae-5b8e-49e2-a466-95e732fe0cc8" version="1">Versatile</content>
	<content contentuid="ac63d1e9-d213-4d75-8828-9c329035e033" version="1">You gain the Skilled Feat or another 1st Level Feat of your choice.</content>




















	<content contentuid="f2dab941-424f-4a28-b33a-4ee30b36bb46" version="1">Whereas tieflings have fiendish blood in their veins, aasimar are the descendants of celestial beings. These folk generally appear as glorious humans with lustrous hair, flawless skin, and piercing eyes. Aasimar often attempt to pass as humans in order to right wrongs and defend goodness on the Material Plane without drawing undue attention to their celestial heritage.  </content>






	<content contentuid="70589719-151e-49ab-af39-b6336074d1b7" version="1">Autumn Eladrin</content>
	<content contentuid="73cfb455-47df-4a28-85f4-71af2008674f" version="1">Winter Eladrin</content>
	<content contentuid="2e10dfe0-36ef-4541-ba49-74682f29627e" version="1">Fey Step</content>
	<content contentuid="32425eae-69a5-4946-9f87-03f959b4e963" version="1">You can choose to use Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma for the saving throw of your effects once your reach 3rd level.</content>
	<content contentuid="aa0ce888-6b0f-4c78-8634-fb5a5e620071" version="1">You have advantage on saving throws you make to avoid or end the charmed condition on yourself.</content>
	<content contentuid="ba6cb4d6-bbc7-4e19-aa83-b3e0cea6fa39" version="1">Seasonal Embrace</content>







	<content contentuid="64fdc691-6785-4d92-9821-bf706828fa31" version="1"></content>
	<content contentuid="bf175981-a2bc-41f5-925d-b09007555d13" version="1">Deep Gnome</content>
	<content contentuid="be34457b-3c63-4820-8cdf-96d1987231bb" version="1">Deep gnomes, or svirfneblin, are natives of the Underdark and are suffused with that subterranean realm’s magic. They can supernaturally camouflage themselves, and their svirfneblin magic renders them difficult to locate. These abilities have enabled them to survive for generations among the perils of the Underdark.</content>
	<content contentuid="639e53ef-46ac-467c-b411-a877a3db4f26" version="1">Forest Gnome</content>
	<content contentuid="3830257d-952c-44ea-87f7-679a6fd7eb28" version="1"> They gather in hidden communities in sylvan forests, using illusions and trickery to conceal themselves from threats or to mask their escape should they be detected. Forest gnomes tend to be friendly with other good-spirited woodland folk, and they regard elves and good fey as their most important allies. </content>
	<content contentuid="f2c739df-7317-434b-a62c-25e2a4068a3b" version="1">Rock Gnome</content>
	<content contentuid="809294b2-41de-47dd-8107-4c18d7893f55" version="1">A gnome's energy and enthusiasm for living shines through every inch of his or her tiny body. As a rock gnome, you have a natural inventiveness and hardiness beyond that of other gnomes.</content>
	<content contentuid="0cd7f307-b168-47d2-826e-861a1fa3e3b1" version="1">The Mark of Detection is an inquisitive’s dream. It sharpens powers of observation and intuition, allowing the bearer to draw connections and interpret clues others might miss. </content>
	<content contentuid="fd59ece7-52d1-4161-9e51-671baa111025" version="1">Wind and water welcome the half-elves who carry the Mark of Storm, and some learn to call on the power of the storm itself.</content>





	<content contentuid="d871dc97-1f4a-46e6-9f20-5031f3a077f6" version="1">Aphaelon</content>
	<content contentuid="1fc97b18-21dd-4712-9743-2b5cd272d22e" version="1"> The Arch Seraph of Temperance holds sway over the domains of peace and spirituality. A patron of monks, clerics, and peacemakers, Aphaelon is honored by those who seek enlightenment.</content>
	<content contentuid="39ab8178-a154-4521-a3cd-5c0de8ec093d" version="1">Beleth</content>
	<content contentuid="ead0dcce-85ff-4d27-842c-16c5cf69f559" version="1"> The Arch Daemon of Fear goes by other names: the Trickster, the Laughing Man, and Blackjester. Beleth’s goal is to spread fear throughout the world, and in this regard he has far surpassed his former master.</content>
	<content contentuid="81df8b55-2ade-419f-931b-d26ed710dbf1" version="1">Malikir</content>
	<content contentuid="4c35475f-a1d1-41c1-b9a4-2ad769f1f42b" version="1"> The Arch Daemon of Pride prefers the title “God”. As the most powerful of the Arch Daemons, her domain is tyranny and the abuse of authority.</content>
	<content contentuid="60d5b4fc-0481-4558-8054-20ef9297446b" version="1">Venin</content>
	<content contentuid="14e0db22-6993-4c53-9a61-a9ef3333f1ec" version="1">The Arch Daemon of Deceit is known as the Great Deceiver, Dusktongue, and Hooded. She is the master of illusion, lies, and insanity. </content>
	<content contentuid="4972fcc1-798d-4fde-a8f2-508259aff045" version="1">Tormach</content>
	<content contentuid="6e9849cb-3d79-4c87-960a-ae5ce5f40c8d" version="1"> The Arch Daemon of Wrath goes by names such as Manslayer and Marauder, as he has taken over the domain of the war god Maligant.</content>
	<content contentuid="1656c83c-75c7-4453-a7f7-9b938149bdc6" version="1">Sitri</content>
	<content contentuid="d3879738-f9d9-429e-97ac-ac3166e60193" version="1"> The Arch Daemon of Hedonism, who is also called Bloodrose and the Tempter, lures mortals to give in to gluttony, lust, and the basest worldly desires.</content>
	<content contentuid="81401091-0458-44fa-a965-0f1fdbe9c6b9" version="1">Gorodyn</content>
	<content contentuid="06bc21df-5551-49fe-a43f-9da956ca8a80" version="1"> The Arch Daemon of Avarice is often called the King of Red Coins. He’s a corrupted follower of Jezra, god of commerce.</content>
	<content contentuid="750be712-fa39-4d70-93fb-aa44956a60d1" version="1">Lady Morrakesh</content>
	<content contentuid="65a7b731-afc1-489c-8b61-b687a4a68078" version="1"> The Burning Lady, Red Queen, and Emberheart are among her many names. The Primordial of fire holds court in her dimension of Flamebourne. She commands azers, efreeti, and fire giants in her army.</content>
	<content contentuid="12ae4623-d3c7-424d-a700-9523d197b64c" version="1">Alondo</content>
	<content contentuid="ca6ee0a4-5a8c-44b2-86da-599a9bd7d815" version="1"> Lord of the Deep and ruler of the Endless Sea, Alondo controls the denizens of lakes and seas. He is worshipped by merfolk, water elementals, and the mighty leviathans.</content>
	<content contentuid="b4f6cfb6-fc7d-41ab-b5c1-24ec2b1f309a" version="1">Citrolach</content>
	<content contentuid="c3963f3c-3545-4c2d-934f-a35835d42928" version="1">The Living Mountain masters over all those who pledge themselves to earth and stone: earth elementals, deep dwarves, and gnomes, as well as all who dwell in his underground realm of Stonereach. His power extends to plants and the denizens of the forests. </content>
	<content contentuid="8bdb96f0-074a-4cb4-b9f7-0186a2d19ca0" version="1">Ilhara</content>
	<content contentuid="f1e2b7a2-be0c-43e2-ba1a-e6b0037c5e28" version="1"> The Queen of Air and Shadow is the most ambitious Primordial of all. She sends her army of djinn, sylphs, and air elementals abroad to find secrets from among mortals and spirits alike.</content>
	<content contentuid="h126089ebg7f3eg4ee1g9bcag73406fa97d22" version="1">Empowered Bite</content>
	<content contentuid="h054af242ged4dg4220g9d3fg025bbd356a97" version="1">When you attack with this bite and hit a creature that isn’t a Construct or an Undead, you can empower yourself.</content>
</contentList>